<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:43:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>


		<item>
			<title>Spiders</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#11</link>
			<description>Little fucker. I'm naked on the toilet and your come at me when I haven't even had my morning coffee? Fuck off with that shit.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
	<a id="11"></a>
		<p>Spiders.</p>
		<p>Friggin' spiders.</p>
		<p>Lots of spiders make their way into the house.</p>
		<p>Like, lots.</p>
		<p>I't gotten so bad I'd find spiders in my bathroom daily.</p>
		<p>And not the cute little spider buddies with webs in a corner that eat pests and want you to leave them alone. Nope. These spiders were quick and mean - oh so mean! - and scurried all over the place. They looked like wolf spiders, but they were black.</p>
		<p>Are there even black wolf spiders?</p>
		<p>And mean. Did I already mention mean? Don't think a spider can be mean? One morning I woke up and blearily made my way to the banister overlooking the stairs so I could tell my wife and kitty i love them. As my hand brushed the railing it bumped something. It barely registered. I was still mostly asleep. I thought to myself, <em>wouldn't it be funny if that was a spider</em>, then yelled down, "Love you!" to my girls. I turned, shuffled my way down the hall, and went into the bathroom.</p>
		<p>I took off my PJs and sat on the toilet, and as I sat there, trying to wake up, I saw this black spider crawl under the door, turn toward me, then run - yes, run - right at me.</p>
		<p>Little fucker. I'm naked on the toilet and your come at me when I haven't even had my morning coffee?</p>
		<p>Fuck off with that shit.</p>
		<p>I grabbed a roll of toilet paper - the only thing at hand - and sent it to its eight-legged maker.</p>
		<p>Shit.</p>
		<p>And these spiders? Whatever kind they are? They don't seem to spin webs. In fact, I've only seen them use spider silk once.</p>
		<p>It was just the other day.</p>
		<p>You see, nowadays, we have a guy come out and spray chemicals all over the inside and outside of the house.</p>
		<p>Chemical warfare! Science! Opposable thumbs, bitches!</p>
		<p>This guy comes out every couple of months. But that last few weeks before the guy comes out again? The spiders start coming 'round.</p>
		<p>But now? Now I'm prepared.</p>
		<p>So, spider silk. Right. Just the other day, I was using the bathroom facilities. I finished my business, stood up, spun the toilet paper roll, and out shot a spider.</p>
		<p>It was waiting for me in the damned toilet paper roll.</p>
		<p>Mother. Fucker.</p>
		<p>But like I said, now? Now I'm prepared. Oh yes, now that I know that these spiders come back a week or two before the chemical warfare guy comes once again to spray chemical arachnid death, I  make sure I have a book at hand.</p>
		<p>A nice, thick, hardcover book with a dust jacket that cleans off easily after morte di ragno.</p>
		<p>I'm a librarian, fuckers! I ain't never running out of books to squash y'all with!</p>
		<p>So the spider popped out the cardboard toilet paper roll and went down it's little silk lifeline to the floor. It ran toward a piece of trim it could scuttle under.</p>
		<p>Bam!</p>
		<p>Down came Stephen King's <cite>Misery</cite> to end its miserable little life.</p>
		<p>There may be lots of spiders, but every time <cite>Misery</cite> comes out? There's one less.</p>
		<br /><br /><br />
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:43:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#11</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.04.22</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#4</link>
			<description>Nunchucks!</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>nunchuckin' while waitin' for the bus.</p>
		<iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Wn5HOTQkDVQ?si=kmEVYJLtB8xBx1Wh" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 10:23:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#4</guid>
		</item>






		<item>
			<title>2025.04.21</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#10</link>
			<description>Divers caught in sperm whale's giant underwater poo cloud</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/newsbeat-30958073">Divers caught in sperm whale's giant underwater poo cloud</a></p>
		<blockquote>
			<p>When Keri Wilk dived into clear waters off the island of Dominica, swimming through a massive whale poo was not in the plan. But it's what happened.</p>
			<p>"At first, it seemed like a regular bowel movement," Keri explained.</p>
			<p>"But rather than continuing its dive down, it remained at the surface and continued to defecate for a startling length of time.</p>
			<p>The "poonado" then spread through the water - ending up in Keri's mouth - as the whale flapped its tail.</p>
		</blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:42:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.1.html#10</guid>
		</item>



	</channel>
</rss>