<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:56:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.10</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#119</link>
			<description>sunday sunday sunday</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Sunday 10 August 2025</p>
		<p>Miles riding: 372. Especially nice ride <a href="https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#118">yesterday</a>.</p>
		<p>Hours writing: 0. Drat. Though I did find an old piece I'd been looking for for years: <a href="https://baki.cc/twas.the.night.before.christmas.html">'Twas the Night Before Christmas</a>. It's a little on the mean side of things but I really enjoy it. Glad I finally found it.</p>
		<p>Notable patron interactions:</p>
		<ul>
			<li>Patron request: combustion libraries. Patron wanted in-state libraries with non-digital primary sources going back a few hundred years. Found options at the <a href="https://www.cookchemlab.com/">University of Oregon</a> and <a href="https://research.engr.oregonstate.edu/blunckgroup/combustion-ignition-radiation-and-energy-laboratory">Oregon State University</a>.</li>
			<li>Middle-school aged patron looking for some specific books went from being so shy around me they could barely speak to joking around with me and calling me Matthew.</li>
			<li>Got another hug. I'm averaging one per week lately.</li>
		</ul>
		<p>During online searches I've been using <a href="https://bing.com">Bing</a> more than <a href="https://google.com">Google</a> lately. The results are better and Google has taken to ignoring basic search parameters (-, "", etc). This has been happening more and more lately.
		<p>More work on <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.html">archivio.antico</a>: <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.herbie/index.html">Herbie</a>, <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.election.2004/index.html">Election 2004</a>, and <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.rutabaga.v2/index.html">Rutabaga v2</a>.</p>
		<p>Decided against moving for now. No Boise and no Flagstaff for us. We have a pretty good life and trying to make it even better by moving to a new place is too much of a gamble. Big risk for minimal gains. We'll continue taking day and weekend trips. We might still move back to the Twin Cities, though, should I ever get a job offer there.</p>
		<p>Decided against embedding offsite media (think youtube vids and the like). Much better privacy-wise. Went through and changed all old embeds with links. Still occasionally embed local media.</p>
		<p>Father memory: Letting me steer the car (from the passenger seat (when I was in grade school)) after swim practice at the high school.</p>
		<p>Snowflake memory: using my suitcase as a bed so often I had to get a second suitcase.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 11:20:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#119</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.09</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#118</link>
			<description>vroom!</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Went for <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/dir/Lincoln+City,+OR/Timber,+OR/45.9020833,-123.7602406/45.709299,-123.8578095/45.6651582,-123.8380518/Lincoln+City,+OR/@45.5534159,-123.6441659,10.31z/data=!4m33!4m32!1m10!1m1!1s0x54ea8d760b76bd77:0x71530e6a7d2ce862!2m2!1d-124.0159354!2d44.9620902!3m4!1m2!1d-123.8298783!2d45.4569653!3s0x54eb2b0819a53bef:0x72022cb2003593a5!1m5!1m1!1s0x5494e5a1524ec1e1:0x1df48d08327d929d!2m2!1d-123.2955437!2d45.7198097!1m0!1m0!1m5!3m4!1m2!1d-123.9322534!2d45.4082587!3s0x54eb28578f2bd465:0xcc7a01aa247653ae!1m5!1m1!1s0x54ea8d760b76bd77:0x71530e6a7d2ce862!2m2!1d-124.0159354!2d44.9620902!3e0?entry=ttu&g_ep=EgoyMDI1MDgwNi4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D">a 200 mile ride</a> today - up 101, over the Coastal Range, up through the Coastal Range, back over the Coastal Range, then down the coast to home. Lots of fun riding and pretty scenery.</p>
		<p>Up over <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oregon_Route_6">Oregon Route 6</a> is one of my favorite rides over the Coastal Range. Well, I lie a little here, they're all my favorite, but they're all favorites for different reasons. Hwy 6 is my favorite because I can hustle through the twists and uneven roads better than most anything on four wheels, so when I ride it on a weekend during the summer with all the tourists heading to and from the coast there's lots of passing to be had.</p>
		<p>Vroom.</p>
		<p>Today I caught up to a loaded down (lots of luggage on the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pillion">pillion seat</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sissy_bar">sissy bar</a>)<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Softail">Harley Softail</a> (not sure which). Woo! They were hustling that <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cruiser_(motorcycle)">cruiser</a> through the curves and around cars like nobody's business.</p>
		<p>I used to have a <a href="https://www.bing.com/search?q=victory+boardwalk">Victory Boardwalk</a>, so I have an appreciation for how they were handling their bike.</p>
		<p>I was enjoying their riding so much I tucked in behind them and watched the show. They'd stand (must've had <a href="https://www.bing.com/search?q=motorcycle+mid+controls">mid-controls</a>, not <a href="https://www.bing.com/search?q=motorcycle+forward+controls">forwards</a>) over the worst of the uneven broken pavement and around curves without slowing; all the more impressive knowing they must've had only three(ish) inches of suspension travel (to my eight). And their <a href="https://www.bing.com/search?q=motorcycle+lean+angle">lean angle</a>? On a Harley like that? Almost nonexistent, and it slowed them down very little.</p>
		<p>Eventually I had to get off 6 to continue my little trip. I caught up with them, threw a <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shaka_sign">shaka</a>, and went on my way.</p>
		<p>And <a href="https://baki.cc/serial.10.html#93">Mabel</a>? Continues to impress. Oodles of ground clearance. Gobs of lean angle. Cruises around politely and hustles with a flick of the throttle.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:51:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#118</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.08</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#117</link>
			<description>no court for you!</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>No jury duty for me.</p>
		<blockquote>
			<p>Disqualification Request Result - Lincoln County Circuit Court Your disqualification was granted. You're no longer required to report for jury. For questions, please contact the court.</p>
		</blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:59:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#117</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.07</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#116</link>
			<description>DS9</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2rhJNy-dCBU">Greatest neon lighting ever.</a></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:01:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#116</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.06</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#115</link>
			<description>DS9</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Man. So uncool. I tried rewatching <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Star_Trek:_Deep_Space_Nine">Star Trek: Deep Space Nine</a> the last couple nights.</p>
		<p>I couldn't do it.</p>
		<p>Didn't enjoy it.</p>
		<p>I mean, it was neat to see the characters again. Actors did a great job acting. Characters were nifty. Sisko? Great! Garak? Fabulous! Dukat? Love to hate to love him! Kira? Spicy! Dax? Fun!</p>
		<p>But, I just didn't care? I can't decide if it's because the plots seemed so contrived (and I know it's always been that way) or if it's because it's such an accurate reflection of what's happening today (we're living it, yo), but I just couldn't.</p>
		<p>Watched the first six episodes. Skipped around a bit in seasons two and three. Watched the first couple episodes when Sisko shaved his head. Dominion war! Founders! Maquis! Klingons!</p>
		<p>Nothing.</p>
		<p>It's a sad, sad day, my friends. A sad day, indeed.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:53:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#115</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#114</link>
			<description>wiby</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
			<p>In the early days of the web, pages were made primarily by hobbyists, academics, and computer savvy people about subjects they were personally interested in. Later on, the web became saturated with commercial pages that overcrowded everything else. All the personalized websites are hidden among a pile of commercial pages. Google isn't great at finding them, its focus is on finding answers to technical questions, and it works well; but finding things you didn't know you wanted to know, which was the real joy of web surfing, no longer happens. In addition, many pages today are created using bloated scripts that add slick cosmetic features in order to mask the lack of content available on them. Those pages contribute to the blandness of today's web. </p>
			<p>The Wiby search engine is building a web of pages as it was in the earlier days of the internet. In addition, Wiby helps vintage computers to continue browsing the web, as pages indexed are more suitable for their performance. </p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:01:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#114</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.04</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#113</link>
			<description>The U.S. government tried denying James Joyce's Ulysses "admittance into the United States." </description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>The U.S. government tried denying <a href="https://search.worldcat.org/search?slug=1108727116&q=ti%3Aulysses+AND+au%3Ajames+joyce">James Joyce's <cite>Ulysses</cite></a> "admittance into the United States." <a referrerpolicy="no-referrer" href="https://law.justia.com/cases/federal/district-courts/FSupp/5/182/2250768/">The government's motion was for a decree of forfeiture and destruction.</a> The judge read the book to determine what was what. Here's some of what he said about it.</p>
		<p>It would've been too difficult for a jury to read it:</p>
			<blockquote>It seems to me that a procedure of this kind is highly appropriate in libels such as this for the confiscation of books. It is an especially advantageous procedure in the instant case because, on account of the length of "Ulysses" and the difficulty of reading it, a jury trial would have been an extremely unsatisfactory, if not an almost impossible method of dealing with it.</blockquote>
		<br />
		<p>The judge liked and loathed the book:</p>
			<blockquote>Furthermore, "Ulysses" is an amazing tour de force when one considers the success which has been in the main achieved with such a difficult objective as Joyce set for himself. As I have stated, "Ulysses" is not an easy book to read. It is brilliant and dull, intelligible and obscure, by turns. In many places it seems to me to be disgusting, but although it contains, as I have mentioned above, many words usually considered dirty, I have not found anything that I consider to be dirt for dirt's sake. Each word of the book contributes like a bit of mosaic to the detail of the picture which Joyce is seeking to construct for his readers. </blockquote>
		<br />
		<p><cite>Ulysses</cite> was sexy but not sexy:</p>
			<blockquote>...reading "Ulysses" in its entirety, as a book must be read on such a test as this, did not tend to excite sexual impulses or lustful thoughts, but that its net effect on them was only that of a somewhat tragic and very powerful commentary on the inner lives of men and women..."Ulysses" may, therefore, be admitted into the United States. </blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:42:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#113</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.03</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#112</link>
			<description>samuel pepys Sunday 03 August 2025</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Sunday 03 August 2025</p>
		<p>Miles ridden this week: 440. Rediscovering some paved(ish) back roads I haven't been on in years.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Hours writing: 0. Blech. Excuse du jour? Trying to get the <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.html">archivio.antico</a> sorted - will take a while.</p>	
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Notable patron interactions from the previous week:</p>
		<ul>
			<li>A patron who read Dostoevsky's <cite><a href="https://search.worldcat.org/title/52578655">The Idiot</a></cite> as a 10-year-old (they liked the title) is now, at 85, reading it again to see what they think of it seven-and-a-half decades later. Wonder if it will hold up.</li>
			<li>Told a patron that they didn't have to go home but they couldn't stay here when we were about a minute from closing. They couldn't decide between three Tom Clancy novels. I told them they should take all three and if there were any they didn't like they'd get their money back. Library humor.</li>
			<li>Got cussed out in two languages by a long-time regular. They started by calling me fucking lazy because I sit at the reference desk all day. I tried explaining that, as a reference librarian, sitting at the reference desk is the majority of my job. They didn't much care for that line of reasoning and went on to explain their position vociferously and multilingually. Let them know they can think whatever they like, but cussing out staff is inappropriate behavior and if they continued they'd have to leave for the day. They continued then left for the day.</li>
		</ul>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Interview with the public library in Flagstaff, AZ. Another cool place. Just like last week, still not sure about pay cut (only ~$25k/yr this time around) and what effect it would have on pension and potential retirement. The conundrum: do we settle for the pretty nifty life we have here and travel lots or possibly hurt our chances of retirement but move around every few years.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Stopped taking two of my four allergy shots a month ago. Starting to feel the negative effects of that decision. Fingers crossed things don't get too bad.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Father memory: We had a football game we'd play: make it across the big back yard (about 30 meters) in four passing plays, then three passing plays, then two passing plays, then in one passing play.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Snowflake memory: slow blinks.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#112</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.02</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#111</link>
			<description>library smell</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>The delight of getting your sense of smell back after days of being sick; the distress of it happening at the public library.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:40:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#111</guid>
		</item>















	</channel>
</rss>