<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:59:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.07</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#150</link>
			<description>e.t. glowing finger ouch.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.bing.com/search?q=e.t.+glowing+finger+ouch">Imagine E.T.'s glowing finger reaching out while saying, "Ouch."</a></p>
		<p>
		<video controls>
			<source src="media/ope.ouch.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video> 
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 12:59:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#150</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.06</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#149</link>
			<description>i'm a daisy.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>A patron told me all people resemble flowers. Evidently I'm a <a href="https://extension.psu.edu/programs/master-gardener/counties/luzerne/news/april-birth-flower-english-daisy-bellis-perennis">daisy</a>.</p>
		<p><img src="media/library.daisy.jpg" alt="Closeup of dozens of daisies with PNW trees looming in the background and an orange garage off to the right side." title="Daisies." /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 23:04:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#149</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#148</link>
			<description>the most riverting 9 minutes in scifi filmdom you'll see this year.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=If-XGaHZSts">The most riveting 9 minutes of scifi filmdom you'll see this year.</a> By <a href="https://linktr.ee/carolineklidonas">Caroline Klidonas</a>.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:37:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#148a</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.04</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#147</link>
			<description>library cat to the big stack o' books in the sky.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.wstx.us/CivicAlerts.aspx?AID=916">Beloved library cat has passed away</a></p>
		<blockquote>
		<p>It is with heavy hearts that we inform you of the passing of Browser, the beloved library cat. Browser passed away peacefully of natural causes. He was one month shy of sixteen years old. In 2010, the Library staff was inspired by the story of Dewey Readmore Books, an Iowa library cat who had a book written about him, and adopted Browser to be a library cat when he was just 1 year old. Browser spent fifteen years of his life at the White Settlement Public Library and was one of their longest tenured employees. Browser brought delight to patrons and employees over the past decade and a half with his playful and curious nature, often cozying up to people while they read and worked. Some of his favorite activities included riding the book return cart while employees returned books to the shelves, stealing the Library Manager’s seat any time she got up, watching bird videos, and hanging with the crafting club any time they met. Browser sat in on so many GED classes at the library that the teacher eventually awarded him an honorary GED. On behalf of the entire Library staff past and present, we would like to thank all who went out of their way to visit Browser, play with him, and remind him how good of a boy he was. He lived a full and joyful life that was filled with friends.</p>
		</blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:30:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#147</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.03</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#146</link>
			<description>sliding houses.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>The perils of building your house on a cliff overlooking the ocean. <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/@44.9592465,-124.0201388,3a,53.2y,352.75h,90.48t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1sg2rg0jEMuYWL_C1GmTQsoA!2e0!6shttps:%2F%2Fstreetviewpixels-pa.googleapis.com%2Fv1%2Fthumbnail%3Fcb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile%26w%3D900%26h%3D600%26pitch%3D-0.4751291567884408%26panoid%3Dg2rg0jEMuYWL_C1GmTQsoA%26yaw%3D352.7454900296222!7i13312!8i6656?entry=ttu&g_ep=EgoyMDI1MDgyNS4wIKXMDSoASAFQAw%3D%3D">What once was this</a> is now this:</p>
		<p><img src="media/pnw.house.unstable.jpg" alt="House built on a cliff overlooking the ocean being deconstructed because of ground shifting." title="House deconstruction." /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:32:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#146</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.02</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#145</link>
			<description>drowning whales</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Many whale die by <a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/heartbreaking-footage-shows-two-young-163454852.html">drowning</a>. Maybe whales who <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cetacean_stranding">beach</a> themselves fear drowning.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:36:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#145</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.01</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#144</link>
			<description>pnw peacock</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><img src="media/pnw.peacock.jpg" alt="Metallic blue and green peacock strutting along a trail in the Coastal Range." title="PNW Peacock." /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 14:02:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#144</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.31</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#143</link>
			<description>the devil by name.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Groovy. Stacy and I got into the acknowledgments for <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/keithrosson.bsky.social">Keith Rosson's</a>, <cite><a href="https://search.worldcat.org/title/1409214280">The Devil by Name</a></cite>, which was a corker of a read.<br /><br />
		<p><img src="media/book.rosson.jpg" alt="Our names highlighted in the book." title="Page of book." /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#143</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.29</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#141</link>
			<description>urine in the ilbrary?</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>A patron is doing a job interview via teleconference on their laptop.</p>
		<p>Must resist urge to sneak up behind patron and give them <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=give+someone+bunny+ears&sca_esv=465159d7bf2b0b64&udm=2&biw=1280&bih=587&ei=G6GwaJ_DH52F0PEPo9auoQc&ved=0ahUKEwjfvLiykq6PAxWdAjQIHSOrK3QQ4dUDCBE&uact=5&oq=give+someone+bunny+ears&gs_lp=EgNpbWciF2dpdmUgc29tZW9uZSBidW5ueSBlYXJzMgYQABgHGB4yBhAAGAcYHjIGEAAYBxgeMgQQABgeSMU9UP8cWP8ccAN4AJABAJgBAKABAKoBALgBA8gBAPgBAfgBApgCAaACBqgCAJgDAYgGAZIHATGgBwCyBwC4BwDCBwMyLTHIBwM&sclient=img">bunny ears</a>.</p> 
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:23:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#141</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.28</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#140</link>
			<description>library bunny ears.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>A patron is doing a job interview via teleconference on their laptop.</p>
		<p>Must resist urge to sneak up behind patron and give them <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=give+someone+bunny+ears&sca_esv=465159d7bf2b0b64&udm=2&biw=1280&bih=587&ei=G6GwaJ_DH52F0PEPo9auoQc&ved=0ahUKEwjfvLiykq6PAxWdAjQIHSOrK3QQ4dUDCBE&uact=5&oq=give+someone+bunny+ears&gs_lp=EgNpbWciF2dpdmUgc29tZW9uZSBidW5ueSBlYXJzMgYQABgHGB4yBhAAGAcYHjIGEAAYBxgeMgQQABgeSMU9UP8cWP8ccAN4AJABAJgBAKABAKoBALgBA8gBAPgBAfgBApgCAaACBqgCAJgDAYgGAZIHATGgBwCyBwC4BwDCBwMyLTHIBwM&sclient=img">bunny ears</a>.</p> 
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:37:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#140</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.27</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#139</link>
			<description>library groupies.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>There are library...groupies? Stalkers? I'm not sure what to call them.</p>
		<p>I guess I'll go with groupies. Stalkers implies some malevolent intent.</p>
		<p>(Though there are library stalkers, too, but this isn't about that.)</p>
		<p>I'm not talking about the vast majority of patrons, most of whom are friendly, many of whom are chatty, and almost all of whom are just happy to be in a library. Groupies are different, though still harmless. Well, mostly.</p>
		<p>It's like this: I'm in an <a href="https://www.indeed.com/career-advice/finding-a-job/front-of-house-vs-back-of-house">FOH</a> <strike>customer</strike> patron service role. I sit at the reference desk eight hours a day, five days a week and help people solve problems without charging them anything for it. It's a great gig. I love that there's no money involved. Since it's a public-facing job I tend to be very patient and optimistic when working with patrons; when someone needs help, yelling and shouting and making them feel stupid for not knowing something is, well, mean and counterproductive.</p>
		<p>Because of my demeanor on the job, sometimes patrons get a little...obsessed? They see a nice, helpful guy who knows a little bit about some stuff. The guy tries to put people at ease and lets them know that just because they don't know this one very specific thing it doesn't make them stupid or worthless. There are, very unfortunately, too many people out there who do not experience much positive human interaction and when they see someone fairly consistently offer others that kind of interaction, they want more of it.</p>
		<p>That's where things get a bit awkward.</p>
		<p>What does 'wanting more of it' look like? They'll spend hours in the library sitting close by, facing you so they can see you interact with others. Oftentimes they'll stare at you for minutes at a time. When you get up from the reference desk they'll intercept you to talk for a brief moment, or, just stand in front of you and wait for you to say something to them. And they'll do it over and over again. Multiple times a day. Multiple days a week.</p>
		<p>It doesn't sound like much, but it's exhausting.</p>
		<p>The best way I've discovered to counter this? Be as boring as possible. (This comes naturally to me.) Be polite. Don't offer up anything personal. Usually after a week or two (or three or, very occasionally, four) they get bored since they see you aren't this ultra-amazing wonderful super-intelligent person, you're just a working stiff like everybody else trying to do your job to the best of your ability. And yes, every once in a while the same person will come back after a couple of months. For, like, a little top off. When this happens they're usually around for a couple of days and then they're gone again.</p> 
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#139</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.26</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#138</link>
			<description>Fog playing in the treetops.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Fog playing in the treetops.</p>
		<p>
		<video controls>
			<source src="media/yard.fog.trees.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video> 
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:02:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#138</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.25</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#137</link>
			<description>different way to look at books.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<blockquote>
			<p>Think not of the books you've bought as a "to be read" pile. Instead, think of your bookcase as a wine cellar. You collect books to be read at the right time, the right place, and the right mood.</p>
		</blockquote>
		<p align="right">- <a href="https://hachyderm.io/@donkersgoed/109616299686783302">Luc van Donkersgoed</a></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:30:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#137</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.24</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#136</link>
			<description>ouch.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Yeah no. No off pavement riding for a week or two. Ouch. Gotta let the ribs heal. Stacy and I will be driving up to the viewpoint this evening. Hopefully get a good pic or two.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#136</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.23</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#135</link>
			<description>giving motorcycle riding a crack.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Thought I'd celebrate today by riding into the Coastal Range and cracking a rib. Mission accomplished.</p>
		<p>Riding off pavement is tough. You have to sit differently. Lean the bike differently. Stand occasionally. Let the motorcycle slip and slide underneath you.</p>
		<p>Last week I dropped Mabel four times, every one of them on a little side trail I've nicknamed Matt's Bane.</p>
		<p>The good news about dropping a bike off pavement is you're generally going slower than street speeds and gravel and dirt is softer (and less road rashy) than pavement.</p>
		<p>The bad news about dropping a bike off pavement is you're generally on a slippery uneven surface which makes footing and leverage a challenge.</p>
		<p>I dropped Mabel about half way up a hill climb. Picking up a 458 pound motorcycle on a dirt hill is tricky. Picking her up on the same hill three more times while trying to get down is even trickier. Bruised the arm and leg a bit.</p>
		<p>This week I thought I'd go back and try again.</p>
		<p>Yeah.</p>
		<p>Every time you hear someone say how smart librarians are remember this story.</p>
		<p>So I went back down Matt's Bane. Then went back down on Matt's Bane. Made it even less far this time. When I went down my left arm got pinned to my side. I landed on it. Mabel landed on me. I heard a crack.</p>
		<p>Job #1? Turn Mabel off. Job #2? Get out from under the 458 pound motorcycle. Job #3? Stay on hands and knees while determining what the crack was. Wrist? OK. Arm? OK. Elbow? OK. Shoulder? OK. Knee? Leg? Ankle? All OK. Clavicle? Okey dokey.</p>
		<p>Oh, look at that, breathing hurts. You know, a skosh. Breathing isn't supposed to hurt.</p>
		<p>Stay on hands and knees for a couple minutes while I contemplate taking up macramé.</p>
		<p>Remember I've never been any good at knots. Drat. Try not to throw up. Check.</p>
		<p>Pain isn't sharp. Yay! Breathing mostly okay. Yay! Manage to stand up. Yay! Pick up bike. Yay! Turn bike around on hill without dropping her again. Yay!</p>
		<p>I get back to the main trail - cuz fuck Matt's Bane, yo - and decide...yeah...to keep going further instead of turning back home.</p>
		<p>Not three minutes later I get to a clearing with a view all the way to the ocean.</p>
		<p>This is why I'm riding off pavement!</p>
		<p><img src="media/andare.nifty.view.jpg" alt="Twelve or so miles inland in the coastal range looking at a fogged in Lincoln City. Cascade Head is on the right. So is god's Thumb." title="Nifty Coastal Range." /></p>
		<p>The pic above was taken with a not-so-great phone. There's <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cascade_Head">Cascade Head</a> on the right. A little to the left is <a href="https://www.bing.com/images/search?q=god%27s+thumb+lincoln+city&form=HDRSC3&first=1">God's Thumb</a>. The thick white(ish) strip along the top of the picture is the sky. The darker gray strip beneath that is the ocean. The thin white strip going from God's thumb across the pic is a fogged in Linclon City. The rest is the Coastal Range.</p>
		<p>I also got a video or two that turned out even worse. I hope to get back up there tomorrow after work with a better camera.</p>
		<p>Yeah. Tomorrow.</p>
		<p>Librarian.</p>
		<p>As I sit here in a comfy chair hopped up on Tylenol typing all this out I wonder if riding off pavement is worth it. I mean, I can get pictures and <a href="serial.15.html#134">videos that look like this from the pavement for goodness sake</a>. 
		<p>I'll see if my courage (and pain management) holds for tomorrow.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 20:54:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#135a</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.22</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.15.html#134</link>
			<description>florence, OR, home of the book Dune, and the explosing whale.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Nice day. Cool and windy on the coast. Excessive heat warning in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Willamette_Valley">the valley</a> for today and tomorrow. Lots of traffic; folk trying to escape the heat. Here's where I turned around right outside of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Florence,_Oregon">Florence, OR</a>, home of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Exploding_whale">the exploding whale</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dune_(novel)">the inspiration for Herbert's <cite>Dune</cite></a>.</p>
		<p>
		<video controls>
			<source src="media/andare.florence.high.up.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video> 
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 20:54:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#134a</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.21</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#133</link>
			<description>not a kwik-e-mart.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>
		<video controls>
			<source src="https://baki.cc/media/library.not.a.kwik.e.mart.mp4" type="video/mp4">
		</video> 
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 11:23:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#133</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.20-2</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#132</link>
			<description>more wkrp in cincinnati.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>I really hope this gets rid of <a href="serial.14.html#131">my earworm</a>, because 24 hours is too much. Oh so very too much.</p>
		<p>Library lyrics for <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=voRoKJSd5Lw">WKRP IN Cincinnati Main Theme</a>:</p>
		<p>
			Baby, if you've ever wondered<br />
			Wondered whatever became of me<br />
			I'm living in the stacks in Lincoln City<br />
			Lincoln City, Driftwood Library<br />
			<br />
			Got kinda tired of packin' and unpackin'<br />
			books from my, own home library<br />
			Maybe you and me were never meant to be<br />
			Just get a library book once in a while<br />
			<br />
			Headin' up that highway, leavin' you behind<br />
			Hardest thing I ever had to do<br />
			Broke my heart in two, to charge you, late fee fines<br />
			The price for findin' books was losin' you<br />
			<br />
			Memories help me hide my lonesome feelin'<br />
			Reading books keeps me from feelin' low<br />
			It's gettin' late, my friend, my love, I miss you so<br />
			Time to close this book, I've gotta go<br />
			<br />
			Baby, if you've ever wondered<br />
			Wondered whatever became of me<br />
			I'm living in the stacks in Lincoln City<br />
			Lincoln City, Driftwood Library<br />
			<br />
			Got kinda tired of packin' and unpackin'<br />
			books from my, own home library<br />
			Maybe you and me were never meant to be<br />
			Just get a library book once in a while<br />
			<br />
			I'm at Driftwood Library in Lincoln City<br />
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:53:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#132</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.20-1</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#131</link>
			<description>wkrp in cincinnati</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=voRoKJSd5Lw">WKRP IN Cincinnati Main Theme</a> by <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WKRP_in_Cincinnati#Musical_themes">Steve Carlisle</a></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:30:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#131</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.20</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#130</link>
			<description>chuck tingle author event.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Went to see Chuck Tingle last night. Was groovy. Bought the new book, <a href="https://search.worldcat.org/title/1452439900"><cite>Lucky Day</cite></a>. $28! Books are so expensive! Thank goodness for libraries, but sometimes you just gotta own the book.</p>
		<p>There was a very enthusiastic crowd. Here we were playing guess the real title of the book. #2 was not it, though I may have to try to write a book with the title, <cite>Slammed by the Four Year Overdue Library Book That I just Found Under My Bed</cite>.
		<p><img src="https://baki.cc/media/ope.chuck.tingle.reading.jpg" alt="Picture of Chuck Tingle in an action pose during his author event." title="Chuck Tingle." /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:25:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#130</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.19-1</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#129</link>
			<description>badminton</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/08/physics-of-badmintons-new-killer-spin-serve/">Physics of badminton’s new killer spin serve </a></p>
		<blockquote>
			<p>Serious badminton players are constantly exploring different techniques to give them an edge over opponents. One of the latest innovations is the spin serve, a devastatingly effective method in which a player adds a pre-spin just before the racket contacts the shuttlecock (aka the birdie). It's so effective—some have called it "impossible to return"—that the Badminton World Federation (BWF) banned the spin serve in 2023, at least until after the 2024 Paralympic Games in Paris.</p>
		</blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:35:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#129</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.19</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#128</link>
			<description>star trek</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="star.trek.html">Star Trek</a></p>
		<blockquote>
			<p>And just how many people would join Starfleet to get selfies that no one else could so they'd get more followers? "Here's me going warp 8." "Here's me in the Borg cube." "Here's me doing the 'get shot by a phaser set to stun' challenge." Would prank vids for Youtube get out of control? Would cadets decompress fellow cadets' space suits during space walks? "Sorry, Cadet Peters, I know your lungs partially ruptured, but it was just a prank, bro! You should've totally exhaled, dude!"</p>
		</blockquote>
		<blockquote>
			<p> Or would it be just too darned hard to log in? Facebook: "We see you're logging in from an unusual star system, we have sent a code to your email, enter it here to continue." Only you ticked off the Comms Specialist by beating them in poker so they are being a little bitch about it and blocking your email from penetrating the shield that is currently up because the Enterprise came across a Romulan Bird-of-Prey in the Neutral Zone.</p>
		</blockquote>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 10:53:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#128</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.18</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#127</link>
			<description>spiders</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Spiders suck.</p>
		<p>Totally suck.</p>
		<p>Absolutely completely utterly suck.</p>
		<p>And I know. I know. We're supposed to be cool with spiders nowadays. Spider Bros, they say. They eat all the pests in your house, they say. They're more scared of you then you are of them, the say.</p>
		<p>You know what I say?</p>
		<p>Get bent spiders!</p>
		<p>I don't know if it's a PNW thing or what, but these big, evil looking spiders that make their way into our house are...not...cool, man!</p>
		<p>This one time, I woke up. Good start to the day, right? Waking up? So I wake up, get out of bed, shuffle my way to the railing overlooking the stairs to the first floor of our house, and, as I put my hands on the railing, still half asleep and eyes mostly shut, my hand brushes something off the railing.</p>
		<p><em>Huh</em>, I think to myself, but, you know, barely, because conscious thought isn't really part of my reality that early in the morning, <em>wouldn't it be funny if that were a spider</em>? And that was it. As soon as I thought the thought I forgot the thought. It dropped out of my consciousness. I yell, "Love you!" to my wife and "Sweet Pea!" to my cat, and, with my day started properly I shuffle off to the bathroom to do bathroom-type things.</p>
		<p>As I sat down on the toilet, I noticed a black blur out of the corner of my eye. I turned my head to see a big black spider crawl under the door and into the bathroom. It stopped, turned toward me, and ran.</p>
		<p>"Bro!" I said.</p>
		<p>It stopped and said, "Sup!"</p>
		<p>I said, "You did not just crawl under the bathroom door to come at me!"</p>
		<p>It replied, "You did not just knock me off that railing!"</p>
		<p>"Bruh," I insisted. "I was asleep! I didn't know you were there!"</p>
		<p>"Well that makes it all okay then doesn't it," it sassed, slowly crawling toward me.</p>
		<p>"Bruh!" I reiterated.</p>
		<p>"Bruv!" It replied, stopping again. "You done fucked around now you're gonna find out!" It ran toward me again.</p>
		<p>"Not cool!" I replied. "I got my drawers down over here trying to take a dump!"</p>
		<p>"Like a bitchass chump," it said, still coming at me.</p>
		<p>"Stop!" I yelled, standing up. "Don't start nuthin, won't be nuthin!"</p>
		<p>"Big talk," it said, then stopped right in front of me. It focused all eight of its eyes on my private parts and continued, "for a little man."</p>
		<p>"You little fucker!" I said as he closed the last of the gap between us.</p>
		<p>"Is that what your wife calls it?"</p>
		<p>I grabbed the box of tissues from the top of the toilet tank behind me and brought it down right on top of it. I lifted the box and saw the spider's legs begin to curl up. It's eyes focused on me briefly, so I said, "Bitch, please," then saw eight points of light fade into darkness.</p>
		<p>Then there was this other time. I was sitting on the toilet again. I don't want to paint too much of a picture here, but I had just finished my business and went to grab toilet paper to, you know, complete the transaction, so I roll the toilet paper and out shoots another big evil spider! Out Of the toilet roll! It drops a little piece of silk on the edge of the roll and it rappels down to the ground then scutters under the nearest floorboard trim.</p>
		<p>It was waiting for me in the toilet paper roll.</p>
		<p>Little fucker.</p>
		<p>It was waiting for me in the toilet paper roll!</p>
		<p>Goddamn arachnids!</p>
		<p>It was waiting...</p>
		<p>...for me...</p>
		<p>...in the toilet paper roll.</p>
		<p>That's how it wants to come at me? When my pants are down around my ankles?</p>
		<p>So yeah, you can talk all you want about ecological balance and spider bros and how beneficial they are and how much better off we are that they're around.</p>
		<p>You're wrong.</p>
		<p>Spiders suck.</p>
		<p>Totally suck.</p>
		<p>Absolutely completely utterly suck.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:05:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#127</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.17</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#126</link>
			<description>weekly samual pepys.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Miles riding: 718. Tried doing some off pavement riding (forest roads and the like) but couldn't because of fire hazards from drought conditions up in the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oregon_Coast_Range">Coastal Range</a>. Did some longer distance riding instead. Also got hand guards and skid plate to make off pavement riding safer for <a href="serial.10.html#93">Mabel</a> when I can use the trails again.</p>
		<p>Hours writing: 0.</p>
		<p>Organized more <a href="archivio.antico.html">archivio.antico</a>: <a href="archivio.antico.trip.2005/index.html">A trip</a> (2005), <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20081103032939/http://www.tinydeadbunny.com/">archive.org link to tiny dead bunny</a> (2006), <a href="archivio.antico.h.2006/index.html">H</a> (from 2006), <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4kHfbuq4MiE">Bullitt Right Along</a> (2007), <a href="archivio.antico.election.2008/index.html">bakiwop for president</a> (2008), <a href="archivio.antico.twitter.2008.html">tweets</a> (2008), and <A href="archivio.antico.fbi.santa/index.html">FBI Santa</a> (2010).</p>
		<p>No hugs this past week from patrons.</p>
		<p>Father memory: My father was a high school teacher. I had him as a teacher. I never knew when he was going to give pop quizzes. My father was sneaky.</p>
		<p>Snowflake memory: Going to IHOP to talk over getting Sweet Pea after visiting her in the shelter for the first time. We rushed back as quickly as we could because we were afraid someone else would choose her.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 20:52:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.14.html#126</guid>
		</item>




















	</channel>
</rss>