<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:00:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.03</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#112</link>
			<description>samuel pepys Sunday 03 August 2025</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Sunday 03 August 2025</p>
		<p>Miles ridden this week: 440. Rediscovering some paved(ish) back roads I haven't been on in years.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Hours writing: 0. Blech. Excuse du jour? Trying to get the <a href="https://baki.cc/archivio.antico.html">archivio.antico</a> sorted - will take a while.</p>	
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Notable patron interactions from the previous week:</p>
		<ul>
			<li>A patron who read Dostoevsky's <cite><a href="https://search.worldcat.org/title/52578655">The Idiot</a></cite> as a 10-year-old (they liked the title) is now, at 85, reading it again to see what they think of it seven-and-a-half decades later. Wonder if it will hold up.</li>
			<li>Told a patron that they didn't have to go home but they couldn't stay here when we were about a minute from closing. They couldn't decide between three Tom Clancy novels. I told them they should take all three and if there were any they didn't like they'd get their money back. Library humor.</li>
			<li>Got cussed out in two languages by a long-time regular. They started by calling me fucking lazy because I sit at the reference desk all day. I tried explaining that, as a reference librarian, sitting at the reference desk is the majority of my job. They didn't much care for that line of reasoning and went on to explain their position vociferously and multilingually. Let them know they can think whatever they like, but cussing out staff is inappropriate behavior and if they continued they'd have to leave for the day. They continued then left for the day.</li>
		</ul>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Interview with the public library in Flagstaff, AZ. Another cool place. Just like last week, still not sure about pay cut (only ~$25k/yr this time around) and what effect it would have on pension and potential retirement. The conundrum: do we settle for the pretty nifty life we have here and travel lots or possibly hurt our chances of retirement but move around every few years.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Stopped taking two of my four allergy shots a month ago. Starting to feel the negative effects of that decision. Fingers crossed things don't get too bad.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Father memory: We had a football game we'd play: make it across the big back yard (about 30 meters) in four passing plays, then three passing plays, then two passing plays, then in one passing play.</p>
			<p align="center">- - -</p>
		<p>Snowflake memory: slow blinks.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#112</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.08.02</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#111</link>
			<description>library smell</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>The delight of getting your sense of smell back after days of being sick; the distress of it happening at the public library.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:40:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.13.html#111</guid>
		</item>















	</channel>
</rss>