<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:28:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>





		<item>
			<title>2025.07.01</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#80</link>
			<description>Pacific sunset.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Pacific sunset.</p>
		<p>
			<video autoplay loop>
				<source src="media/ope.lazy.sunset.mp4" type="video/mp4">
			</video>
		</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 12:28:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#80</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.06.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#79</link>
			<description>pnw life.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>The PNW is a pretty funky place to live. The Oregon Coast doubly so.</p>
		<p>There's the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oregon_Coast_Range">Oregon Coast Range</a> which butts right up against the Pacific Ocean. It frequently hails. It frequently rains when it's sunny. This leads to oodles of rainbows. Moss and molds abound. Deciduous trees are never bare and brown. If there aren't leaves on them there's moss. Lots of moss.</p>
		<p>Fungi also abound. Mushrooms grow everywhere.<p>
		<p>The temperature generally stays between forty and seventy degrees fahrenheit. It rarely snows. When it does it doesn't stick around long. It's a wet cold. This makes it feel much colder than it is. We're used to the dry colds back home. The moisture means hair is flat.</p>
		<p>There's a lot of salt in the air. Every couple of months we need to wash the house down to get the salt (and keep the moss) off. If cars are left outside surface rust happens very quickly. Keeping them in a garage seems to ameliorate this issue.</p>
		<p>There doesn't seem to be a level place in the joint. Hills up the wazoo. It's a good thing it rarely gets cold enough for water to freeze because with all the water we get around here and all the hills we have, driving or biking or walking would be difficult.</p>
		<p>It really does rain a lot. Heavy rains abound. Winds blow and gust hard, well into the double digits. When the winds blow and the rain thunders down...it's some nice moody weather. There are all kinds of lights rains, too. There is little lightning and thunder.</p>
		<p>All this is mostly true for the first 1/4 to 1/2 mile of land from the ocean. While much of it rings true for the rest of the Coastal Range as well, there are differences. For instance, it can get much warmer there in the summer and much snowier in the winter.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 14:52:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#79</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.06.29</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#78</link>
			<description>Practice Random Acts of Reading.</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Practice Random Acts of Reading.</p>
		<p><img src="https://baki.cc/media/library.reading.jpg" alt="Hung print of a woman with long, red hair pulling a red wagon filled with books. There is a double sidewalk with a fancy white picket fence. Behind the fence are hundreds of tall flowers threatening to overflow the fence. A couple of the books have fallen from the wagon. One book, having fallen face up, is being read by a little brown cat. A little gray cat is in front of the woman, looking back. Text on the print reads Practice Random Acts of Reading." title="practice random acts of reading" /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 15:17:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.9.html#78</guid>
		</item>














	</channel>
</rss>