<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/baki.rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
		<description>Caveat Lector</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:14:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en-us</language>





		<item>
			<title>2025.10.01-b</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#177</link>
			<description>library creepy caller census</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://old.reddit.com/r/Libraries/comments/1lwvpoq/we_need_a_creepy_caller_census/">Library Creepy Caller Census</a></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:14:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#177</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.10.01</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#176</link>
			<description>federal funding</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><cite><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=phHe6aNcocQ">Federal Funding</a></cite> by <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cake_(band)">Cake</a>.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:14:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#176</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#175</link>
			<description>dumbass</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>My wife is very into hockey (she's from Minnesota, dontchaknow) and just told me this: <a href="https://apnews.com/article/wild-kirill-kaprizov-contract-df38df3d649600ff7d953da19ac8acbb">Minnesota Wild sign Kirill Kaprizov to richest deal in NHL history: $136 million over 8 years</a>.</p>
		<p>My first thought? I'm not sure I would trade 8 years of my life for $136 million.</p>
		<p>Which just goes to show what a dumbass I am.</p>
		<p>My instincts tell me to say no (and I don't seem to be paying attention to the more logical parts of my brain (which is, usually, par for the course)).</p>
		<p>Just colossal dumbassery on my part.</p>
		<p>But no matter which way I look at it, if my current job - and let me tell you I have a pretty plum gig - offered me $136 million to stay for eight more years? I'd say no.<sup>1</sup></p>
		<p>It just feels wrong.</p>
		<p>It doesn't matter that I would still be below retirement age at the end of the 8 year contract and could retire early. It doesn't matter that I would make roughly $136 million more dollars for 8 years of work than if I worked those same 8 years at my current (with step increases) salary. It doesn't matter that I would be <em>lucky</em> - oh so very lucky - to be able to keep my job for the next 8 years at all.</p>
		<p>None of that matters.</p>
		<p>What seems to matter? I don't know. But good for Kaprizov. He seems smarter than me. And richer. Younger. More athletic. Probably nicer. And? And my wife is very happy that he'll be playing for the Wild.</p>
		<br />
		<p><sup>1</sup>My wife, god bless her, would soon set me straight, though.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:38:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#175</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.29</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#173</link>
			<description>handwashing</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>I wonder what <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ignaz_Semmelweis">Ignaz Semmelweis</a>, the physician in 1800s Hungary who was shunned, mocked, fired, beaten, suffered a nervous breakdown, and killed for suggesting healthcare workers should wash their hands to reduce postpartum mortalities that were three times higher than midwives (who did wash their hands), would think of this comic found in a doctor's examination room?</p>
		<p><img src="media/ope.handwashing.jpg" alt="Cartoon depicting a superhero telling people to wash their hands to fight infection." title="Handwashing is your superpower!" /></p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#173</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.24</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#172</link>
			<description>hiccup cure</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p>Cure hiccups by getting a glass of water and a pen or pencil. Place the pen or pencil inside your mouth and lightly bite down on it. Drink the glass of water.</p>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:39:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#172</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.23</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#171</link>
			<description>got up previously wrriten write ups (and one new one)</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="viaggio.12.html">Wrote up the visit to Dee Wright Observatory.</a></p>
		<p>Also got the following previously written write ups up:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><a href="viaggio.5.html">Mt. Rainier. Mt. St Helens.</a></li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.6.html">The Olympic Peninsula</a></li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.7.html">King Tides</a> (not quite a trip but definitely trippy)</li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.8.html">Jedediah Smith State Park (CA)</a></li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.9.html">2017 Total Eclipse</a> (not quite a trip but definitely trippy)</li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.10.html">Joseph Oregon and the Wallowas</a></li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.11.html">Echo Fire Complex</a> (does evacuating count as a trip?)</li>
				<li><a href="viaggio.13.html">Timberline</a></li>
			</ul>
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:21:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.27.html#171</guid>
		</item>





		<item>
			<title>2025.09.22-b</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/serial.24.html#168</link>
			<description>debate me bro</description>
			<content:encoded>
<![CDATA[
		<p><a href="https://www.techdirt.com/2025/09/17/the-debate-me-bro-grift-how-trolls-weaponized-the-marketplace-of-ideas/">The “Debate Me Bro” Grift: How Trolls Weaponized The Marketplace Of Ideas </a></p>
		<blockquote>
			<p>The “debate me bro” playbook is simple and effective: demand that serious people engage with your conspiracy theories or extremist talking points. If they decline, cry “censorship!” and claim they’re “afraid of the truth.” If they accept, turn the interaction into a performance designed to generate viral clips and false legitimacy. It’s a heads-I-win-tails-you-lose proposition that has nothing to do with genuine intellectual discourse.</p>
			<p>The fundamental issue with “debate me bro” culture isn’t just that it’s obnoxious, it’s that it creates a false equivalence between good-faith expertise and bad-faith trolling. When you agree to debate someone pushing long-debunked conspiracy theories or openly hateful ideologies, you’re implicitly suggesting that their position deserves equal consideration alongside established facts and expert analysis.</p>
		</blockquote>
		<blockquote>
			<p>Perhaps most insidiously, these aren’t actually debates at all. They’re performances designed to generate specific emotional reactions for viral distribution. Participants aren’t trying to persuade anyone or genuinely engage with opposing viewpoints. They’re trying to create moments that will get clipped, shared, and monetized across social media.</p>
			<p>Kirk perfected this grift. As a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zn0_2iACV-A">recent detailed analysis of one of Kirk’s debates</a> demonstrates, when a student showed up prepared with nuanced, well-researched arguments, Kirk immediately tried pivoting to culture war talking points and deflection tactics. When debaters tried to use Kirk’s own standards against him, he shifted subjects entirely. The goal was never understanding or persuasion—it was generating content for social media distribution.</p>
		</blockquote>
		<br /><br /><br />
]]>
			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:21:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/serial.24.html#168</guid>
		</item>


























	</channel>
</rss>