<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:08:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>Late January</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#024</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Most every year, late January is a time of sun on the coast. We seem to get a week or two reprieve to the otherwise very rainy, very wet season. I've been told that with the sun comes the cold. This year it's proven to be true as we've hit the 30s every night for the past week and a half.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:08:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#024</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.21</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#023</link>
			<description>

				#www - Star Trek: TNG supperware set. Could American Evangelicals Spot the Antichrist? Finding personal websites. ellesho.me.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#023</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.20</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#022</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - From Chapter 31: The Poor People's Campaign of the Autobiography of Martin Luther King Jr., "And I come by here to say that America too is going to hell if she doesn't use her wealth. If America does not use her vast resources of wealth to end poverty and make it possible for all of God's children to have the basic necessities of life, she too will go to hell."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:15:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#022</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.18</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#021</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Beach Hazards Statement. Cold Weather Advisory.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 17:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#021a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2017 Eclipse</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-12.html</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - I didn't catch the roar (scream?) when it began, but it all happened at once from a dead silence. It was creepy and exhilarating. It was a grab you by the amygdala and flood your body with adrenaline kinda thing....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-12.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Crater Lake</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-11.html</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Small write up on a visit to Crater Lake from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-11.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Wallowas</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-10.html</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Small write up on a visit to the Wallowas from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:43:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-10.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.16</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#020</link>
			<description>

				#ope - We bought a sports package recently. Stacy wanted to start watching more sports. She decided on ESPN+ and has been watching hockey a few times a week. It brings her back to her Minnesota roots....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:59:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#020</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>