<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:39:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.09</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#009</link>
			<description>

				#ope - #ope

Sick day yesterday taking care of Stacy. I was to be the driver should she have needed to go to the hospital. Neither of us thought she would need to go to the hospital, but since we're not medical professionals we thought we'd both take a day off just in case. You know, you can't be too careful with these things....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:39:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#009</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Martian Chronicles Read By Leonard Nimoy</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#008</link>
			<description>

				#www - Ray Bradbury's There Will Come Soft Rains read by Leonard Nimoy.....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#008</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Daisy</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#007</link>
			<description>

				#library - A patron told me that all people resemble flowers and I'm a daisy. According to the Penn State Extension Master Gardener Program:....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:41 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#007</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -1</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-1.html</link>
			<description>

				These #yard entries are from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate them into the current journal, I'm putting them here. I like them too much to leave them out but am too lazy to integrate them properly, so here they lay. All new #yard posts will show in the regular journal....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:40 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-1.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -2</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-2.html</link>
			<description>

				These #library entries are from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate them into the current journal, I'm putting them here. I like them too much to leave them out but am too lazy to integrate them properly, so here they lay. All new #library posts will show in the regular journal....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:39 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-2.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -7</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-7.html</link>
			<description>

				The Echo Mountain Complex Fire took place over a week or so in 2020. This entry begins on 6 September. Not my best writing, but it's too gosh darned long to rewrite while being important enough to want to remember. Not all the links below work anymore....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:37 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-7.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ann Telnaes</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - I've worked for the Washington Post since 2008 as an editorial cartoonist. I have had editorial feedback and productive conversations—and some differences—about cartoons I have submitted for publication, but in all that time I’ve never had a cartoon killed because of who or what I chose to aim my pen at. Until now....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 16:20:38 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</link>
			<description>

				#yard #pnw - Coast Guard helicopter out of Depoe Bay responding to emergencies up and down the coast. Happens frequently on weekends and holidays. Get a great view of it from the bedroom window....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 18:10:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>First Three Books of the Year</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</link>
			<description>

				#books - Finished Wild Massive. Finished The Return. DNF'd The 25th Hour....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:24:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</link>
			<description>

				#ope #pnw - It's our 29th anniversary. We love snow. We enjoy The Shining (and The Shining and The Shining). What better place to go than Timberline Lodge on Mt. Hood?...

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>