<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:25:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.15</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#025</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Coastal Hazard Message. National Weather Service.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 20:25:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#025</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Plaid Pantry</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#024</link>
			<description>

				#writing - Added a new story, Plaid Pantry, to The Little Oregon Book of Horrors. 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 09:07:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#024</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Rejection</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#023</link>
			<description>

				#books - DNF'd Rejection by Tony Tulathimutte. Very well written book. Only made it through the second story, Pics, though. After reading it I was in a funk, didn't even realize it until Stacy asked me if I was okay. After that I decided to drop the book. But such good writing! 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:59:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#023a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ocean Dip</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#022</link>
			<description>

				#pnw  - This guy walks down the bluffs to the ocean for a dip every day. Winter. summer. Rain. Shine. In only a swimsuit.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 13:20:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#022</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Harleys Angels: The Strange and Terrible Saga of the Middle-Aged Motorcyclist</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/harleys.angels.html</link>
			<description>

				#writing  - He wobbled to a stop, barely able to hold up the 850 pound chrome monster while getting the kickstand down. "Brothers!" he yelled, fist bumping the waiting trio. "Brother!" they harrumphed ...and having validated their Harleyness they mounted their rolling metal and made noise...booming stentorian noise ...and pulled out past children holding their hands to their ears and parents clucking their tongues in disapproval – for this is what they lived for, making the world know they were the biggest and loudest bad asses on the planet and their passage would be marked through sound of exhaust, shine of chrome, and drip of oil.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 14:06:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/harleys.angels.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Fosse Fosse</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#021</link>
			<description>

				#wwww  - Walk it out Fosse. Mexican Breakfast Fosse.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:37:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#021</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Luna(cy)</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#020</link>
			<description>

				#yard  - The moon, she follows me.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:29:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#020</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dewey 382.3</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#019</link>
			<description>

				#dewey  - Dewey 382.3 - International Commerce: Commrecial Policy.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 21:18:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#019</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.12</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#018</link>
			<description>

				#pnw #library #ope #earworm  - It took me years to find good meat out here. When i finaly did? So good. There's this butcher's south of Newport. It's in the back of a rundown industrial park. Loads of abandoned buildings with dead loading docks. Mountains of used tires. Rusted out semi trailers galore. Meandering dirt road between enormous piles of scrap metal. The only sign you're finally in the right place is this bloody plastic strip sheeting covering one of the loading dock entrances. You climb rickety stairs, slide between the stained plastic, and find yourself in front of a small fiberboard counter with a fifty year old cash register on it. You yell for a bit until one of the butchers hears you over their bandsaws. They come over, wiping their bloody hands on their bloody leather aprons, grunt at you, take your order, grunt at you again, then go in back. They come out a couple minutes later with your meat. Cash only. Darn good meat. I really hope it's not human.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#018</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.10</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#017</link>
			<description>

				#minnesota #www - Astronomers Suspect Colliding Supermassive Black Holes Left the Universe Awash in Gravitational Waves. A river runs through Hockeytown USA, and you can skate on it for miles. Oklahoma Moms Locked Up for Their Abusers’ Violence Might Finally Get a Break.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 21:35:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#017</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bluesky(s) are here</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#016</link>
			<description>

				#meta - I have a friend, a lazy lazy friend, who is always on Bluesky and never checks my site, so I made this for them: https://bsky.app/profile/baki.cc.web.brid.gy. It's kinda like rss but for Bluesky, so all they have to do is follow the account.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 18:29:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#016</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Snow Emergencies!</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#015</link>
			<description>

				#minnesota - Minneapolis and St. Paul have declared snow emergencies. Woot!

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#015</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Doritos Bag</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#014</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Bought some, what, foreign Doritos? Slightly out-of-market Doritos? Gray market Doritos?

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 15:11:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#014</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1st Annual Kill Kitty Day</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#013</link>
			<description>

				#ope - We euthanized Snowflake one year ago. Because we did the right thing, and because she was such an amazing part of our lives, and because she was family (not the kind of family where we're fur parents and she's our fur baby... that's not my bag), and because we're trying to celebrate all that, I'm calling today Kill Kitty Day.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 21:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#013</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sixteen More Years</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#012</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Only sixteen more years until retirement.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#012</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Axolotls and Trump</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#011</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Two things I don't understand peoples' admiration of and fascination with: Axolotls and Trump.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#011</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Perfect Son</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#010</link>
			<description>

				#books - DNF'd The Perfect Son by Freida McFadden.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 15:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#010</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>