<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Mon, 9 Oct 2023 14:57:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Sliding</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#sliding</link>
			<description>

				"All right," Hector said. "It's just a little further to the scenic lookout. Let's see how fast Jolly Green can get us there." He threw it in drive, stomped the accelerator, and...Jolly Green sputtered, lurched forward a couple feet, then died. "Not a word," said Hector, cranking the ignition and stomping the gas pedal. "You say a bad word about Jolly Green right now and he'll never start for us. I'm serious. You can disrespect Nirvana," said Hector, pointing a finger at Paul, "you can be irreparably hoodwinked by that funky Minneapolis sound, but you must never utter a disparaging word against Jolly Green." 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 9 Oct 2023 14:57:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#sliding</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: It's Oregon</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#its.oregon</link>
			<description>

				"Maybe we'll make...shit...I forgot there's a McMenamins over here," said Julius. They stopped thirty feet from the crowd pouring out of the restaurant. Staff and customers lined the sidewalk, shoulder-to-shoulder four rows deep, in front of them. Adult customers held forks and butter knives. Kids held plastic sporks menacingly. Staff held pots, pans, and butcher knives. Their mouths set. Their eyes determined. 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2023 10:57:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#its.oregon</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Death by Toilet Paper</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#death.by.toilet.paper</link>
			<description>

				He'd been sleeping hard lately, having pulled oodles of doubles at Georgia-Pacific pumping out all the extra toilet paper people were clamoring for in the first weeks of Coronavirus (Commodavirus, his coworkers gleefully called it...Brown Gold) so when his wife started pounding on the front door, screaming his name at three in the morning, he registered it only in his dream – a quiet morning fishing on the Siletz River turned Walmart-wide, no holds barred TP fracas.  

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2023 9:05:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#death.by.toilet.paper2</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Family Picnic</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#family.picnic</link>
			<description>

				Stephen slept the entire day away. All 24 hours of it. The FaceTime notification chime didn't stand a chance at waking him up. Nor did the FaceTime voicemail notifications, the email notifications, the text notifications, the phone call ringtone set to Yakety Sax, or the phone's voicemail notifications. Some time during the early morning he'd begun exhaling crimson red spores.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2023 9:45:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#family.picnic</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: I Got Wood</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#i.got.wood</link>
			<description>

				Ted and the rest of the gang had dubbed themselves the Dirty Dozen for this long weekend on the Oregon Coast. Their mission? Keep Nick as drunk and happy as possible while celebrating the finalization of his divorce from his wife of four and a half months.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2023 10:39:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#i.got.wood</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: .22</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html</link>
			<description>

				"Okay. I'm gonna grab something from my fanny pack, then we have to rush toward the bears making ourselves as big as we can while yelling at the top of our lungs." "That," said Ryan, "does not sound like it should be Plan A."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2023 15:36:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tech Support</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/tech.support.html</link>
			<description>

				The last warbird tried to jump to warp, but succeeded only in collapsing the artificial singularity that powered its warp-drive system, reversing time for all baryonic matter on the ship - adults became children then babies then zygotes while the various ship materials broke down into their component parts until there was only a slightly warbird-shaped cloud of atomic and subatomic particles left hanging in space. "Intriguing," said Data, breaking the astonished silence of the bridge crew.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:38:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/tech.support.html</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>