<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>baki</title>
		<link>https://baki.cc</link>
		<description>caveat lector</description>
		<atom:link href="http://dallas.example.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		<language>en-us</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 11:00:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
		<item>
			<title>2025.03.20</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope2025.03.html#03</link>
			<description>#pnw</description>
			<content:encoded>

<p>Forget the Twin Cities, we need to move to the Cascades: <a href="https://www.statesmanjournal.com/story/news/2025/03/19/winter-storm-warning-snow-oregon-cascades/82555316007/">Winter storm warning issued for 1 to 3 feet of snow on Oregon Cascade mountain roads</a></p>
<p align="center">&nbsp;&nbsp;<span class="divide">~</span>&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.hereisoregon.com/places/2025/03/oregon-town-named-one-of-the-safest-spring-break-destinations-in-the-us.html">Oregon town named one of the safest spring break destinations in the U.S.</a><p>
<blockquote>
One of our state’s go-to spring break destinations, Cannon Beach, was recently named one of the safest spring break destinations in the U.S. in a new trending study that identified several threats to travelers. 
</blockquote>
<p>Back home we say we're going to the lake. That's because it's 90 degrees out and we're eventually gonna hop in the lake to cool off and have some fun. Out here they say they're going to the beach. Because the ocean in Oregon will kill you - riptides, sneaker waves, diamond hard volcanic rock, and an entire ocean of things that will eat you. Alive or dead. And the water is about 45 degrees so nobody goes into the water anyway. And the air temperature is about 55 degrees... if you're lucky... and the 20 mph wind is blowing sand all over the place. I'm not sure why people go to the beach on spring break around here. I mean, people set up tents on the beach to get out of the wind and the stinging sand and the cold. I once saw a couple of teenagers wearing swimsuits - this was about eight years ago - and I couldn't believe there were people brave enough to try that. 

			</content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope2025.03.html#03</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>