<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 16:21:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>Ann Telnaes</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - I've worked for the Washington Post since 2008 as an editorial cartoonist. I have had editorial feedback and productive conversations—and some differences—about cartoons I have submitted for publication, but in all that time I’ve never had a cartoon killed because of who or what I chose to aim my pen at. Until now....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 16:20:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</link>
			<description>

				#yard #pnw - Coast Guard helicopter out of Depoe Bay responding to emergencies up and down the coast. Happens frequently on weekends and holidays. Get a great view of it from the bedroom window....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 18:10:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>First Three Books of the Year</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</link>
			<description>

				#books - Finished Wild Massive. Finished The Return. DNF'd The 25th Hour....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:24:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</link>
			<description>

				#ope #pnw - It's our 29th anniversary. We love snow. We enjoy The Shining (and The Shining and The Shining). What better place to go than Timberline Lodge on Mt. Hood?...

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Year</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#0000000002</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Stacy thought she'd celebrate the new year by doing the polar bear plunge thing. Except we live on the Oregon Coast, so it's cold and rainy and windy but not snowy or icy....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#0000000002</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.02</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#0000000001</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Any time you start thinking the world is a fair and just place, remember this picture. How a schlub like me ended up with an amazing, wonderful, beautiful, intelligent, fun person like this is proof it's an unfair universe/multiverse....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 13:00:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#0000000001</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.28</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000023</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Forgot to mention, when we got Frango mints (which are gone now, natch) from Macy's a couple of days ago we went to a mall to do it. Malls were the bomb diggity back in the day....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 21:50:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000023</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.27</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000022</link>
			<description>

				#ope - I had nightmares last night. First time in I don't even know how long....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:17:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000022</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Christmas Day in the PNW</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000021</link>
			<description>

				#pnw #backyard #ope - Rudolph chilling, listening to More Bounce to the Ounce, in the backyard after a hard night's work (with special guest appearance by plastic pink flamingo #1)....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 16:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000021</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.25</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000020</link>
			<description>

				#ope - “We feel like we’re good at giving people an experience that elevates their dignity, that makes them feel special,” he said. “If you do it carefully and you pay attention to the details, there’s an opportunity to blend people together. And when we all start hanging out together, we just start to understand each other better. That’s really what I am hoping for.”...

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 01:16:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000020</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>It's Both Parties</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000019</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - The Republican Party and the Democratic Party both suck. There is no lesser evil. They are both evil. We keep letting them tell us the other party is the problem. The problem is that we believe that. The problem is that we should be keeping our party honest, not blaming the other parties....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 20:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000019a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.24</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000018</link>
			<description>

				#ope - It's not a very charitable feeling. There's very little 'good will towards men' in it. Santa may leave me a lump of coal. But...I am so proud of myself for cultivating a relationship with my boss where they completely ignore me in everything personal, including Christmas greetings, while still communicating with me professionally when necessary....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:50:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000018a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>I Want a Hippopotamus for Christmas</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000017</link>
			<description>

				#earworm - I Want a Hippopotamus for Christmas by Gayla Peevey....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:56:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00001.html#0000000017</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>