<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:06:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>Keep the Peace</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#017</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - Carter and Mondale are generally considered to be good men (a single example, and, interestingly enough, they post about MLK a bit later). That's the issue. Telling the truth? Fine and good. Obey the law and keep the peace? Not good.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:06:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#017</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Banana Slug Party</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#016</link>
			<description>

				#yard - ain't no party like banana slug party cuz banana slug party don't stop

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:28:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#016</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Gospel According to Matthew Chapter 16</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#sixteen</link>
			<description>

				#gospel - That was some good loaves and fishes," said Joseph, licking his fingers as he and Mary walked back to their beach towels. "Our Boy can burn."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 12:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#sixteenb</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hodge Podge</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#015</link>
			<description>

				#www - RSS, Personal Sites, Climate Lawsuits, Social Media, Public Domain Day, and More

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 21:28:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#015</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.14</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#014</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Finished chapters 14 and 15 of The Gospel According to Matthew....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:16:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#014</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Gospel According to Matthew Chapter 15</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#fifteen</link>
			<description>

				#gospel - Golly Gee did mumble under his breath, "You are the salt of the earth, but if the salt lo- no. No. That won't work. Maybe... whoever slaps you on your right cheek, turn the other. No. Hmmm..."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:15:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#fifteen</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Gospel According to Matthew Chapter 14</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#fourteen</link>
			<description>

				#gospel - Golly Gee and his crew left the Sea of Honalee and traveled two hours inland where they met a large gathering of people. Golly Gee raised his hands and said, "Most assuredly..."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:14:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.gospel.according.to.matthew.html#fourteen</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.13</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#013</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Always weird when I have a Sunday/Monday off of work. Yesterday we went to Newport, OR's Nye Beach, a trendy little area with lots of shops and restaurants and art galleries. It's cool because it has narrow streets and the shops are all right up against each other and there are hidden alleys and sidewalks everywhere. When we moved out here.....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:03:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#013</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.12</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#012</link>
			<description>

				#ope - A couple few months ago I had a revelation. I was talking with my wife. I told her the world was a horrible place and I was going to be... and then there was a mental blur, a shift, a kind of visual sound? 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 15:50:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#012</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>King Tides</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-9.html</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - Small write up on king tides from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays. The image above is The Great Wave off Kanagawa by Katsushika Hokusai.....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:51:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-9.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.11</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#011</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - The PNW is a pretty funky place to live. The Oregon Coast doubly so.....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:50:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#011</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Devil by Name</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#010</link>
			<description>

				#books - And, kinda nifty, Stacy and I got into the acknowledgments for this one....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:07:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#010</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Jedediah Smith Redwoods State Park</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-8.html</link>
			<description>

				Small write up on a visit to Jedediah Smith State Park in California from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 12:46:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-8.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mt. Rainier and Mt. St. Helens</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-6.html</link>
			<description>

				Small write up on a visit to the Olympic Peninsula from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 10:46:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-6.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Olympic Peninsula</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-5.html</link>
			<description>

				Small write up on a visit to the Olympic Peninsula from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 10:42:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-5.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Alvord Desert and Steens Mountains</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-4.html</link>
			<description>

				Small write up on a visit to the Alvord Desert and the Steens Mountains in Southeast Oregon from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate it into the current journal, I'm putting it here. I like it too much to leave it out but am too lazy to integrate it properly, so here it lays.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:42:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-4.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Libs-Or Emails</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-3.html</link>
			<description>

				A series of emails sent to Libs-Or, a "forum for sharing information about the Oregon library community."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 17:41:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-3.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.09</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#009</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Sick day yesterday taking care of Stacy. I was to be the driver should she have needed to go to the hospital. Neither of us thought she would need to go to the hospital, but since we're not medical professionals we thought we'd both take a day off just in case. You know, you can't be too careful with these things....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:39:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#009</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Martian Chronicles Read By Leonard Nimoy</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#008</link>
			<description>

				#www - Ray Bradbury's There Will Come Soft Rains read by Leonard Nimoy.....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#008</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Daisy</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#007</link>
			<description>

				#library - A patron told me that all people resemble flowers and I'm a daisy. According to the Penn State Extension Master Gardener Program:....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:41 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#007</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -1</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-1.html</link>
			<description>

				These #yard entries are from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate them into the current journal, I'm putting them here. I like them too much to leave them out but am too lazy to integrate them properly, so here they lay. All new #yard posts will show in the regular journal....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:40 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-1.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -2</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-2.html</link>
			<description>

				These #library entries are from a previous iteration of this journal. Rather than integrate them into the current journal, I'm putting them here. I like them too much to leave them out but am too lazy to integrate them properly, so here they lay. All new #library posts will show in the regular journal....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:39 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-2.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...A Life: Page -7</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00000-7.html</link>
			<description>

				The Echo Mountain Complex Fire took place over a week or so in 2020. This entry begins on 6 September. Not my best writing, but it's too gosh darned long to rewrite while being important enough to want to remember. Not all the links below work anymore....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 16:38:37 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00000-7.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ann Telnaes</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</link>
			<description>

				#mattifesto - I've worked for the Washington Post since 2008 as an editorial cartoonist. I have had editorial feedback and productive conversations—and some differences—about cartoons I have submitted for publication, but in all that time I’ve never had a cartoon killed because of who or what I chose to aim my pen at. Until now....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 16:20:38 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#006</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</link>
			<description>

				#yard #pnw - Coast Guard helicopter out of Depoe Bay responding to emergencies up and down the coast. Happens frequently on weekends and holidays. Get a great view of it from the bedroom window....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 18:10:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#005</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>First Three Books of the Year</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</link>
			<description>

				#books - Finished Wild Massive. Finished The Return. DNF'd The 25th Hour....

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 17:24:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00003.html#004</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2024.12.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</link>
			<description>

				#ope #pnw - It's our 29th anniversary. We love snow. We enjoy The Shining (and The Shining and The Shining). What better place to go than Timberline Lodge on Mt. Hood?...

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:09:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00002.html#0000000001</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>