<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:55:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.12</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#018</link>
			<description>

				#pnw #library #ope #earworm  - It took me years to find good meat out here. When i finaly did? So good. There's this butcher's south of Newport. It's in the back of a rundown industrial park. Loads of abandoned buildings with dead loading docks. Mountains of used tires. Rusted out semi trailers galore. Meandering dirt road between enormous piles of scrap metal. The only sign you're finally in the right place is this bloody plastic strip sheeting covering one of the loading dock entrances. You climb rickety stairs, slide between the stained plastic, and find yourself in front of a small fiberboard counter with a fifty year old cash register on it. You yell for a bit until one of the butchers hears you over their bandsaws. They come over, wiping their bloody hands on their bloody leather aprons, grunt at you, take your order, grunt at you again, then go in back. They come out a couple minutes later with your meat. Cash only. Darn good meat. I really hope it's not human.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 15:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#018</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.10</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#017</link>
			<description>

				#minnesota #www - Astronomers Suspect Colliding Supermassive Black Holes Left the Universe Awash in Gravitational Waves. A river runs through Hockeytown USA, and you can skate on it for miles. Oklahoma Moms Locked Up for Their Abusers’ Violence Might Finally Get a Break.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 21:35:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#017</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Bluesky(s) are here</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#016</link>
			<description>

				#meta - I have a friend, a lazy lazy friend, who is always on Bluesky and never checks my site, so I made this for them: https://bsky.app/profile/baki.cc.web.brid.gy. It's kinda like rss but for Bluesky, so all they have to do is follow the account.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 18:29:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#016</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Snow Emergencies!</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#015</link>
			<description>

				#minnesota - Minneapolis and St. Paul have declared snow emergencies. Woot!

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#015</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Doritos Bag</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#014</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Bought some, what, foreign Doritos? Slightly out-of-market Doritos? Gray market Doritos?

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 15:11:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#014</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1st Annual Kill Kitty Day</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#013</link>
			<description>

				#ope - We euthanized Snowflake one year ago. Because we did the right thing, and because she was such an amazing part of our lives, and because she was family (not the kind of family where we're fur parents and she's our fur baby... that's not my bag), and because we're trying to celebrate all that, I'm calling today Kill Kitty Day.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 21:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#013</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sixteen More Years</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#012</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Only sixteen more years until retirement.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 21:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#012</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Axolotls and Trump</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#011</link>
			<description>

				#ope - Two things I don't understand peoples' admiration of and fascination with: Axolotls and Trump.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:19:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#011</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Perfect Son</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#010</link>
			<description>

				#books - DNF'd The Perfect Son by Freida McFadden.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 15:44:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#010</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>More 2025.02.04</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#009</link>
			<description>

				#www - Comet Atlas Caught in the Act of Disintegration. Wikenigma - an Encyclopedia of Unknowns. Archaeologists Are Finding Dugout Canoes in the American Midwest as Old as the Great Pyramids of Egypt. @_elena@mastodon.social. How Does a Caterpillar Turn into a Butterfly? Why Americans Don’t Walk: A Forgotten Centennial.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 12:04:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#009</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.04</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#008</link>
			<description>

				#yard - Snow yesterday. Snow today. Forecast says snow through Saturday.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 10:54:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#008</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.02.01</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#007</link>
			<description>

				#library - Went to a copyright conference in Portland yesterday. PSU. Kinda cool being in a bigger city again. Lots of life. Chaos. Totes fun. The conference was very informative and well done. The presenters were interesting and fun. Stacy came along and worked in the library. We walked around campus. Ate street food. Got lost. Good times.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:02:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#007</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>2025.01.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#006</link>
			<description>

				#library - Two potentially stress inducing occurrences at work this morning. Opened the door. Boom! There they were. Sneaky little buggers. Hadn't even opened yet. But I'm feeling fine. Easy breezy. The library mellow has returned.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:45:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#006</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Final Sunny Day for a While</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#005</link>
			<description>

				#pnw - We've had four straight weeks of sun on the coast. Tomorrow the clouds and rain return.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:43:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#005</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Smell</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#004</link>
			<description>

				#library - I once wrote something on Facebook, something like, "the delight of getting your sense of smell back after days of being sick; the distress of it happening at the public library."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 12:06:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope00004.html#004</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>