<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/rss.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
			<atom:link href="https://baki.cc/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
			<title>baki</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/</link>
			<description>Caveat Lector</description>
			<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:10:42 PDT</lastBuildDate>
			<language>en-us</language>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2024.01.05</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#05</link>
			<description>

				One of the perils of working in a public library is the number of patrons who try to recommend books to you. It's sweet. It's kind. It's thoughtful. It means that you are making a connection with the patron. Making them feel comfortable. This is a good thing. And I wish to the flying spaghetti monster in beer volcano heaven above that they'd stop.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:10:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#05</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2024.01.03</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#03</link>
			<description>

				This is Snowflake on the Oregon coast, and I'm meowing at whoever's listenin' here. Just remember what ol' Tenacious C does when she car rides, and the vet's poison syringes plunge into her body, and the pillars of heaven shake. Yeah, Great White just looks that big ol' vet right square in the eye and she says, "Give me your best shot, pal. I can take it."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 19:49:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#03</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2024.01.02</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#02</link>
			<description>

				"Introverts often try to push against their nature, having bought into the myth that extroversion is 'better' and that it's the American way."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 17:11:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#02</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2024.01.01</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#01</link>
			<description>

				I'm not doing the New Year's resolution thing this year. I'd say I'm resolving not to do it but that would be, you know, counterproductive. So instead this year I'm making a New Year's wish. I wish to be absurdly rich, monetarily speaking. A little self-centered? Perhaps lacking in goodwill toward all? I see how you could come to that conclusion. That's a fair cop. I can dig it. I don't particularly care in this particular instance, but I get it. I figure we've all been making resolutions for decades and, well, the world at a macro level is pretty shit, right?

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 02:03:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202401.html#01</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2023.12.31</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#31</link>
			<description>

				I think, technically, you could throw New Year's Eve, Advent, and Christmas Eve into the mix as well. I especially love Christmas Eve, makes me think of dark nights softly lit by Christmas trees while snow gently falls outside (though, not so much since we've moved out here). Advent might be cheating a bit, but any time I can open a little door and get a chocolate treat for a couple of weeks is a good holiday in my books. New Year's Eve? Good-natured drunken revelry with lots of laughter, shouting and/or banging of pans.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 11:14:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#31</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2023.12.30</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#30</link>
			<description>

				We met at work, a plasma collection facility on University Avenue in St. Paul. She worked up front prepping donors and I worked in back sticking 'em with needles and hooking them up to the plasma collection machines. We worked second shift. When we got off work we'd hang out at the Barnes and Noble in Har Mar Mall til they closed then we'd go walk around Como or Lake of the Isles or Bde Maka Ska. After a couple of months she moved in with me and bing bang boom here we are 28 years later.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 05:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#30a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Ope...a life: 2023.12.29</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#29</link>
			<description>

				Being 18 1/2, she has many health problems. Two weeks ago we thought we were going to lose her, but our girl is a fighter...always has been. She's tenacious, another nickname for her is Tenacious C. She died once on an operating table about six years ago, turns out she was allergic to the anesthesia they gave her. They came out, told us, then asked us if we wanted them to try and resuscitate her. Our answer was, "Yes, please."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 15:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/ope202312.html#29a</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Evil Tomes: How to Circulate Your Possessed Book Collection</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#evil.tomes</link>
			<description>

				Once the patron gets to the right place in the book, exit the study room quickly. There are a couple of reasons for this: 1) You don’t want to be hanging around while the patron does their thing – patron privacy extends to their use of evil tomes, too. 2) Once you’ve seen Cthulhu summoned a dozen or more times, it gets kinda boring. Come on, Chtulhu, we get it, you’re a Lovecraftian cosmic horror...nice tentacles there, bud. 3) You do not want to be in the room if the patron messes up the incantation. Worst case scenario? You can hear the janitors grumble as they clean up your remains with a sponge. Best case scenario? The patron accomplishes what they set out to because they were all sneaky and used you as their human sacrifice.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:55:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#evil.tomes1</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Dag, yo</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#dag.yo</link>
			<description>

				And it was that 'yo' that I'd just thought that made me realize I couldn't just kill myself, I had to kill him, too...him and all the other vampire gangster wannabes. They were all like him. He'd infected us with a blood curse and gangster wannabe speech. They said things like, "Yo!" and "Tru dat!" There were thousands of them, and if I could take him out, it would kill every other vampire ever created. Including me. 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 12:42:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#dag.yo1</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Rocky Marriage</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#rocky.marriage</link>
			<description>

				I sat in that waiting room. Stared at the wall blankly. Processed. Did you know a cubic meter of water weighs a ton? I didn't. That's around 2,000 pounds of water in a box just over three feet wide by three feet high by three feet deep. Two of those boxes of water weigh more than a Toyota RAV4 or a BMW 5-series. An ocean's worth of water on one side and a coast of basalt rock in front of it? Yeah. That'd do some damage. 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:48:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#rocky.marriage</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Sliding</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#sliding</link>
			<description>

				"All right," Hector said. "It's just a little further to the scenic lookout. Let's see how fast Jolly Green can get us there." He threw it in drive, stomped the accelerator, and...Jolly Green sputtered, lurched forward a couple feet, then died. "Not a word," said Hector, cranking the ignition and stomping the gas pedal. "You say a bad word about Jolly Green right now and he'll never start for us. I'm serious. You can disrespect Nirvana," said Hector, pointing a finger at Paul, "you can be irreparably hoodwinked by that funky Minneapolis sound, but you must never utter a disparaging word against Jolly Green." 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 9 Oct 2023 14:57:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#sliding</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: It's Oregon</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#its.oregon</link>
			<description>

				"Maybe we'll make...shit...I forgot there's a McMenamins over here," said Julius. They stopped thirty feet from the crowd pouring out of the restaurant. Staff and customers lined the sidewalk, shoulder-to-shoulder four rows deep, in front of them. Adult customers held forks and butter knives. Kids held plastic sporks menacingly. Staff held pots, pans, and butcher knives. Their mouths set. Their eyes determined. 

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:57:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#its.oregon</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Death by Toilet Paper</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#death.by.toilet.paper</link>
			<description>

				He'd been sleeping hard lately, having pulled oodles of doubles at Georgia-Pacific pumping out all the extra toilet paper people were clamoring for in the first weeks of Coronavirus (Commodavirus, his coworkers gleefully called it...Brown Gold) so when his wife started pounding on the front door, screaming his name at three in the morning, he registered it only in his dream – a quiet morning fishing on the Siletz River turned Walmart-wide, no holds barred TP fracas.  

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:05:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#death.by.toilet.paper2</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: Family Picnic</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#family.picnic</link>
			<description>

				Stephen slept the entire day away. All 24 hours of it. The FaceTime notification chime didn't stand a chance at waking him up. Nor did the FaceTime voicemail notifications, the email notifications, the text notifications, the phone call ringtone set to Yakety Sax, or the phone's voicemail notifications. Some time during the early morning he'd begun exhaling crimson red spores.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 09:45:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#family.picnic</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: I Got Wood</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#i.got.wood</link>
			<description>

				Ted and the rest of the gang had dubbed themselves the Dirty Dozen for this long weekend on the Oregon Coast. Their mission? Keep Nick as drunk and happy as possible while celebrating the finalization of his divorce from his wife of four and a half months.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 10:39:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html#i.got.wood</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Little Oregon Book of Horrors: .22</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html</link>
			<description>

				"Okay. I'm gonna grab something from my fanny pack, then we have to rush toward the bears making ourselves as big as we can while yelling at the top of our lungs." "That," said Ryan, "does not sound like it should be Plan A."

			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 15:36:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/the.little.oregon.book.of.horrors.html</guid>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tech Support</title>
			<link>https://baki.cc/tech.support.html</link>
			<description>

				The last warbird tried to jump to warp, but succeeded only in collapsing the artificial singularity that powered its warp-drive system, reversing time for all baryonic matter on the ship - adults became children then babies then zygotes while the various ship materials broke down into their component parts until there was only a slightly warbird-shaped cloud of atomic and subatomic particles left hanging in space. "Intriguing," said Data, breaking the astonished silence of the bridge crew.

			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:38:42 PDT</pubDate>
			<guid>https://baki.cc/tech.support.html</guid>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>