<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
 <rss version="0.91">

 <channel>
 <title>¡bakiwop for president!</title>
 <link>http://www.bakiwop.com</link>
 <description>walking for president because running is too much damned work</description>
 <language>en-us</language>

 <image>
 <title>&#161;bakiwop for president!</title>
 <url>http://www.bakiwop.com/images/bakiwoprss.jpg</url>
 <link>http://www.bakiwop.com</link>
 <width>144</width>
 <height>144</height>
 </image>

<item>
 <title>13 May 2008</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080513</link>
 <description>
				&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.time.com/time/printout/0,8816,1739251,00.html"&gt;Time magazine's seven steps to beating obama &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;blockquote&gt;
					Sometimes you don't need the secret memo, a Deep Throat source, or the combination to the safe to get the story. Sometimes it's lying right there in front of you, a series of fragments ready to be pieced together.
 					&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					Such is the case when it comes to John McCain's general election strategy for defeating Barack Obama. For weeks now, the Arizona senator's campaign has been laying its cards on the table, spelling out a strategy for November. Here's a look at seven of their key strategies. 
				&lt;/blockquote&gt;
				I hereby announce my one step plan for beating all candidates: win. 
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2008 09:24:55 CST</pubDate>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>09 May 2008</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080509</link>
 <description>
	&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.boston.com/news/politics/politicalintelligence/2008/05/mccain_gives_mo.html"&gt;McCain gives money back to PAC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;blockquote&gt;
		PAC treasurer Steve Voeller said the excess in-kind contributions were an oversight and notified the McCain campaign, which said it wrote a $1,896.52 check to reimburse the committee for the excess contribution.
	&lt;/blockquote&gt;
	I promise that if you &lt;a href="givememoney.html"&gt;give me money&lt;/a&gt; I will not - no matter how immoral, illegal or unpopular - return a dime of it. To anybody.  Ever.  That's how dedicated I am to getting and keeping your money.  That's how dedicated I am to being your President.
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
	- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2008 11:03:54 CST</pubDate>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>07 May 2008</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080507</link>
 <description>
				Obama has his Rev. Jeremiah Wright - &lt;a href="http://www.clarionledger.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20080505/NEWS/805050339/1001/news"&gt;USA created HIV to infect minorities&lt;/a&gt;. 
				McCain has his Rev. John Hagee - &lt;a href="http://thedailyvoice.com/voice/2008/05/why-oprah-left-obamas-church-000513.php"&gt;Catholic Church "the great whore" and Hurricane Katrina hit to punish New Orleans for a gay march&lt;/a&gt;. 
				Clinton has her Rev. Dean J. Snyder - &lt;a href="http://frontpagemagazine.com/Articles/Read.aspx?GUID=84352487-41FB-4A77-B521-C365CC13BFF9"&gt;recent praise for Jeremiah Wright as "an agent of racial reconciliation"&lt;/a&gt;.
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Let it be known that bakiwop '08 (because there's no election in '09) is currently interviewing for the position of crazy campaign minister - someone who can garner headlines and state inflammatory and insane comments with passion, dedication, righteousness and a straight face.  Must claim I am their greatest friend while netting me millions of campaign dollars and who won't care how much I make fun of - and distance myself from - them.
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				The position will remain open until filled.  bakiwop '08 is an equal opportunity employer.  Please send a large campaign contribution with every application (and apply as many times as you would like).
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

				&lt;a href="contact.html"&gt;If interested contact bakiwop campaign headquarters.&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 15:00:00 CST</pubDate>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>06 May 2008</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080506</link>
 <description>
				&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.voanews.com/english/2008-05-04-voa16.cfm"&gt;Clinton, Obama Stress Democratic Party Unity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;blockquote&gt;
					"Both Senator Obama and I have made it very clear that we will have a unified Democratic Party going into the fall elections," said Hillary Clinton. "I have said that I would work my heart out for him [if Obama is the nominee]. He has said he would do the same for me [if I am the nominee]."
					&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
					"I want a Democrat to win in November," said Barack Obama. "So even if Senator Clinton were the nominee instead of me, I would still be campaigning for Democrats."
				&lt;/blockquote&gt;

				Senator Clinton  continued, "First things first, though - Primaries to the death!"
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Senator Obama, "No. To the pain."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Clinton, "I don't think I'm quite familiar with that phrase."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Obama, "I'll explain and I'll use small words so that you'll be sure to understand, you warthog faced buffoon."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Clinton. "That may be the first time in my life a man besides my husband has dared insult me."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Obama, "It won't be the last. To the pain means the first thing you will lose will be your feet below the ankles. Then your hands at the wrists. Next your nose."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

				Clinton, "And then my tongue I suppose, I beat you too quickly in Pennsylvania. A mistake I don't mean to duplicate in Indiana."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Obama, "I wasn't finished. The next thing you will lose will be your left eye followed by your right."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Clinton, "And then my ears, I understand. Let's get on with it."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Obama, "Wrong! Your ears you keep and I'll tell you why. So that every shriek of every child at seeing your hideousness will be yours to cherish. Every babe that weeps at your approach, every woman who cries out, 'Dear God! What is that thing,' will echo in your perfect ears. That is what to the pain means. It means I leave you in anguish, wallowing in freakish misery in the Senate forever."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Clinton, "I think your bluffing."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				Obama, "It's possible, Pig, I might be bluffing. It's conceivable, you miserable, vomitous mass, that I only lost in Pennsylvania because I lacked the votes. But, then again... perhaps I have the votes after all."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

				Obama, "Drop... Your... Candidacy."
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 07:30:00 CST</pubDate>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>¡Cinco de Mayo!</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080505</link>
 <description>
				&#161;Feliz Cinco de Mayo mis amigos Mexicanos y Latinos!  Yo quiero que tu sabes que yo tengo dos anos de Espanol en highschoolo y yo remebero  mis estudios muy bueno y porque de ese you soy un amigo de todos.  Por favor, vota para mi en la eleccion porque yo speako su langua.  &#161;Esto es correcto - yo soy un amigo de todos los illegos!
				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 08:34:12 CST</pubDate>
 </item>

<item>
 <title>01 May 2008</title>
 <link>http://bakiwop.com/#20080501</link>
 <description>
				&lt;h3&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2008/04/29/AR2008042902397.html?hpid=opinionsbox1"&gt;Landing the White Whale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;blockquote&gt;
					The relationship between Barack Obama and the white working class is beginning to resemble that between Ahab and the white whale. In state after state (Ohio, Pennsylvania and now Indiana), Obama sets out to reel in his working-class quarry, and, in state after state, it eludes him. As Obama is still the likely nominee, many Democrats fear that come November, working-class whites will pull Obama and their party down to defeat.
				&lt;/blockquote&gt;

				Might I suggest, Senator Obama, that little would grab the attention of the American People like a harpoon to the leg.

				&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
				- Vote often, vote bakiwop
 </description>
<pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2008 07:45:19 CST</pubDate>
 </item>


 </channel>
 </rss>